Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Newsletter Collection, 1910-2005 RL.00733
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Ford Motor Co.: Dealers of New England: 1953 June 1
Ford Motor Co.: Direct mail campaign: 1953 July 6
Ford Motor Co.: Exports--Sao Paulo: 1954 Aug. 2
Ford Motor Co.: Falcon: 1960 May 25; 1962 May 9.
Ford Motor Co.: Falcon wagons: 1960 Mar. 9
Ford Motor Co.: Fashion promotion: 1961 Oct. 11; 1959 Oct. 21.
Ford Motor Co.: FoMoCo garages: 1957 May 6
Ford Motor Co.: Ford Motor Co. Theatre television programming: 1953 June 15
Ford Motor Co.: Galaxie Rodeo: 1962 Feb. 14
Ford Motor Co.: Galaxie: 1958 Dec. 3
Ford Motor Co.: Genuine parts: 1953 Mar. 30
Ford Motor Co.: Global testing: 1957 Nov.4
Ford Motor Co.: Hazel television series: 1961 Sept. 20
Ford Motor Co.: International: 1955 May 30; 1961 Jan. 25.
Ford Motor Co.: Juvenile campaign: 1947 Nov.17
Ford Motor Co.: Lincoln Division: 1947 Apr.14
Ford Motor Co.: New international campaign: 1958 May 12
Ford Motor Co.: Peanuts campaign: 1959 Dec. 23
Ford Motor Co.: Peanuts comics: 1960 Oct. 26
Ford Motor Co.: Post-war models: 1952 Nov.10
Ford Motor Co.: Quality campaign: 1951 Dec. 24
Ford Motor Co.: Safety booklet--Buenos Aires: 1961 June 14
Ford Motor Co.: Spanish television: 1960 Feb. 24
Ford Motor Co.: Star Jubilee: 1955 Nov.21
Ford Motor Co.: Taunus 15M--Frankfurt: 1955 Mar. 21
Ford Motor Co.: The Lively Ones/television: 1962 July 27
Ford Motor Co.: Thunderbird: 1954 Aug. 9; 1961 Jan. 18; 1962 Feb. 28.
Ford Motor Co.: Tractors--Sao Paulo: 1952 Dec. 8
Ford Motor Co.: Trucks: 1947 May 26; 1948 Jan. 12; 1950 July 3; 1951 Mar. 19; 1951 Oct. 1; 1953 Mar. 16; 1957 Feb. 4.
Ford Motor Co.: Victoria model: 1950 Nov.20; 1951 Feb. 19.
Ford Motor Co.: Year-end Closeout: 1955 June 27
Foundation for Commercial Banks: 1959 Oct. 28; 1960 Sept. 21; 1959 June 10.
New client: 1958 Sept. 1
Francis DuPont (2nd income campaign): 1958 July 7
Friden Calculation Machine: 1951 Mar. 12
Garrett Corp.: 1949 May 23
Garrett Corp.: AiResearch Division: 1948 July 5
Garrett Corp.: Award-winning campaign: 1958 June 30
Garrett Corp.: Project Mercury: 1959 July 8
Gate City Sash & Door Co.: 1954 Mar. 8
General Cigar Co. (White Owl): 1948 July 12
General Electric (First television commercial in Peru--Lima): 1958 Oct. 27
General Time Corp.: 1951 Aug. 27
General Time Corp.: Seth Thomas: 1952 Sept. 29
Goodyear (Mile Per Tyre): 1962 Aug. 22
Grace & Co. (Recipes--Santiago): 1962 Jan. 10
H.H. Hixon & Co: 1954 Apr.19
Harrod's--Buenos Aires: 1946 Nov.25
Holly Sugar: 1948 June 28
Horlicks Ltd.--London: 1951 Sept. 3; 1957 Feb. 18.
Horlicks Ltd.--London: Powdered malted milk: 1961 Mar. 15
Indiana Bell Telephone Co.: 1948 May 10; 1952 Sept. 8.
Industria Nacional de Neumaticos (Insa batteries--Santiago): 1953 May 11
Institute of Life Insurance: 1946 Aug. 26; 1947 Dec. 8; 1948 Sept. 13; 1953 Oct. 5; 1954 Sept. 13; 1955 Sept. 19; 1958 May 5; 1961 Sept. 27.
Institute of Life Insurance: Fight Inflation: 1957 Oct. 7
Institute of Life Insurance: Inflation campaign: 1959 Mar. 18
Institute of Life Insurance: Newspaper campaign: 1951 Jan. 8
Institute of Life Insurance: Public relations: 1947 July 28
International Agricultural Corp. (Ac'cent--Montreal): 1952 Aug. 18
International Minerals & Chemicals (Ac'cent): 1949 Dec. 12
Irving Trust:
Irving Trust: First national campaign: 1960 Jan. 13
Irving Trust: Home and Abroad series: 1960 Sept. 14
J. Walter Thompson Co.:
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Blood bank: 1953 Nov. 9; 1954 Nov. 22; 1954 Nov. 8; 1956 Feb. 20.
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Canadian Markets--Toronto: 1958 Sept. 8
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Census book: 1951 Nov. 5
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Local television: 1956 Sept. 3
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Publicity: 1961 Nov. 1
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Radio: 1948 Nov. 29
J. Walter Thompson Co.: Special publications service: 1950 Dec. 25
J.B. Williams: 1952 May 19
J.B. Williams: Ice Blue aftershave: 1956 Nov. 26
J.B. Williams: Lectric Shave: 1947 Jan. 20; 1948 Aug. 9.
J.B. Williams: Skol Tan: 1956 Apr. 30
JerClaydon, Inc. (Carpet cleaner): 1952 Sept. 15
Jimmy Durante Show: 1961 Aug. 2
Johns-Manville Corp.: 1947 June 30; 1949 Nov. 28; 1951 Dec. 3.
Johns-Manville Corp.: Brick Upon Brick: 1952 Oct. 6
Johns-Manville Corp.: Celite: 1956 Oct. 1
Johns-Manville Corp.: Min-K insulation: 1958 Mar. 24
Johns-Manville Corp.: Mrs. America campaign: 1959 Jan. 14
Johns-Manville Corp.: Plant City campaign: 1947 Nov. 24
Johnson Motors:
Johnson Motors: Boat Crossed Atlantic: 1958 Aug. 11
Johnson Motors: Bob Hope: 1958 June 9
Johnson Motors: King Features series: 1961 June 7
Johnson Motors: Outboard motors: 1956 Oct. 22
Johnson Motors: Junior Pentagon: 1954 Feb. 8
Kellogg's:
Kellogg's: Corn Flakes--Sydney: 1954 Mar. 29
Kellogg's: English Breakfast--London: 1954 Mar. 15
Kingsberry Mobile Homes:
Kingsberry Mobile Homes: 48% Sales Increase: 1962 Jan. 10
Kingsberry Mobile Homes: Space Houses: 1960 June 1
Kraft: 1946 Nov. 11; 1949 Apr. 11; 1950 Apr. 17; 1950 Feb. 27; 1952 May 5.
Kraft: 6-page editorial advertisements: 1959 May 20
Kraft: Caramels: 1948 June 7
Kraft: Cheese: 1948 Feb. 23
Kraft: Cottage cheese: 1951 Jan. 29
Kraft: Deluxe Slices cheese: 1949 Aug. 8
Kraft: Dine-Out campaign: 1957 Mar. 4
Kraft: Hermes trophy: 1961 June 21
Kraft: Latin American market: 1956 May 21
Kraft: Mayonnaise: 1947 Aug. 25
Kraft: Merchandising record: 1958 Mar. 10
Kraft: Miracle Whip: 1958 Apr. 28; 1958 Feb. 24; 1948 Aug. 30.
Kraft: Orange juice: 1955 Dec. 19
Kraft: Puerto Rican television--San Juan: 1957 July 29
Kraft: Regional foods: 1961 May 3
Kraft: Restaurant sweepstakes: 1957 June 17; 1959 July 22.
Kraft: TV Theatre: 1953 Dec. 21; 1955 Feb. 7.
Labatt Brewery:
Labatt Brewery: Monteal: 1957 Apr. 15
Labatt Brewery: Toronto--Beer and ale: 1954 Jan. 25
Labatt Brewery: Toronto--Tourism, public service: 1947 Mar. 31
Langendorf United Bakeries (Butter-Nut bread): 1948 June 21
Lever Brothers: 1949 June 6; 1952 Jan. 21.
Lever Brothers: Chlorodent: 1953 Aug. 31
Lever Brothers: Gold Foil package: 1955 May 23
Lever Brothers: Lux: 1948 Mar. 8; 1952 Jan. 7.
Lever Brothers: Lux dish soap: 1957 Oct. 21
Lever Brothers: Lux Flakes: 1949 Dec. 26; 1951 Jan. 1.
Lever Brothers: Lux liquid: 1953 Apr. 13
Lever Brothers: Lux soap--Antwerp: 1957 Sept. 30
Lever Brothers: Lux toilet soap: 1948 Aug. 2
Lever Brothers: Lux Video Theatre: 1954 Aug. 23
Lever Brothers: Mrs. Butterworth: 1961 Dec. 13
Lever Brothers: Shampoo: 1952 June 16
Lever Brothers: Skin purifier in Lux: 1959 Nov. 18
Lever Brothers: Stripe toothpaste: 1961 Feb. 16
Lever Brothers: Surf detergent--Canada: 1949 Sept. 5; 1951 May 7.
Lever Brothers: Unilever/Persil soap powder--London: 1951 Oct. 15
Libby, McNeill & Libby: 1950 Jan. 23
Libby, McNeill & Libby: Baby foods: 1956 Aug. 6; 1947 Aug. 18; 1948 Aug. 16.
Libby, McNeill & Libby: Corn: 1959 Sept. 30
Libby, McNeill & Libby: Corned beef hash: 1948 July 19
Libby, McNeill & Libby: Minted pineapple: 1959 Aug. 19
Libby, McNeill & Libby: Talking Books: 1955 Dec. 19
Liggett & Myers: 1961 Nov. 22
Liggett & Myers: Chesterfield cigarettes: 1961 Sept. 13
MAGGI Institutional (Unify Products--Frankfurt): 1962 Feb. 14
Magna Engineering Corp. (Shopsmith): 1948 July 26
Massachusetts Hospital Service (Blue Cross): 1947 Jan. 6
Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Co.: 1950 Sept. 18; 1951 Sept. 24; 1954 Dec. 6.
Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Co.: 100th Anniversary: 1951 May 21
Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Co.: Focus on Babies: 1958 Sept. 29
Mattel (Prince Valiant campaign): 1954 May 17
McGraw Edison:
McGraw Edison: New client: 1957 Sept. 9
McGraw Edison: Voice Writer: 1961 May 24; 1958 July 21.
Mentholatum: 1947 Nov. 10; 1948 Oct. 18; 1949 Sept. 26; 1954 Oct. 18.
Merchandising Groups: 1955 July 18
Metal Box Co. of South Africa--Johannesburg: 1952 July 7
Millers National Federation: 1948 Aug. 23; 1949 Sept. 12.
Mirror: 1948 Sept. 27
Mobile Home Manufacturers Association: 1959 Sept. 2
Mobile Home Manufacturers Association: Newlyweds, retirees: 1958 Apr. 21
Mobile International (Step emblem): 1961 Feb. 8
Murine:
Murine: Eye drops/ Reader's Digest: 1961 Mar. 15
Murine: Plastic Bottle campaign: 1959 Aug. 12
Mutual Orange Distributors: 1952 Mar. 17
National Book Committee, Inc. (Library Week): 1958 Mar. 17
National Car Rental (Men Who Hate toWait campaign): 1961 Sept. 20
National Library Week (Color bookmark): 1961 Apr. 12
National Shoe Institute: 1949 July 4
National Trailways Bus System: 1951 May 28
NATO: 1959 June 3
New Holland Machine Co.: 1950 Dec. 18; 1951 Dec. 31.
New Holland Machine Co.: Farm machines: 1954 Feb. 15
New Holland Machine Co.: Model 66 baler: 1953 Mar. 2
New Holland Machine Co.: Modular farm machine: 1961 Apr. 5
New York Central Railroad: 1955 May 16
North Western Mutual Life Insurance: 1948 Nov. 22
Northeast Airlines:
Northeast Airlines: Every Hour campaign: 1960 Sept. 7
Northeast Airlines: Viscount service: 1958 Aug. 18
Northwestern Mutual: 1957 Oct. 14
Oneida Limited: 1955 Mar. 7
Oneida Limited: Father/Daughter campaign: 1956 Aug. 27
Oneida Limited: Heirloom Sterling: 1949 Feb. 28; 1953 Aug. 3; 1953 June 8.
Oneida Limited: Premier and Deluxe: 1957 Aug. 5
Oneida Limited: Public relations: 1960 Mar. 16
Oneida Limited: Replacement market: 1957 May 27
Oscar Mayer & Co.: 1962 Sept. 19
Oscar Mayer & Co.: Family Personality: 1961 June 14
Owens-Illinois Glass Co.: 1946 Aug. 19; 1949 May 30; 1952 Apr. 7; 1954 June 28.
Owens-Illinois Glass Co.: Duraglass: 1948 Mar. 1; 1950 July 10.
Owens-Illinois Glass Co.: Kimble: 1953 Feb. 2
Owens-Illinois Glass Co.: Libbey: 1946 Sept. 16; 1948 Jan. 26; 1950 Sept. 25; 1951 Apr. 2; 1952 Nov. 17; 1953 Jan. 19.
Owens-Illinois Glass Co.: Summer holiday campaign: 1958 May 19
Oxford University Press: 1947 Nov. 3; 1949 Apr. 4; 1950 June 19.
Pacific Mills: 1951 Aug. 20
Pacific Mills: Carpet: 1953 Aug. 10
Pacific Mills: Fitted sheets: 1956 Jan. 16
Pacific Mills: Menswear: 1955 Aug. 8
Pacific Mills: Sheets: 1954 Dec. 13
Pan American World Airways: 1951 Sept. 10; 1956 June 11; 1957 Dec. 16; 1960 Oct. 12.
Pan American World Airways: Atlantic: 1958 Sept. 22
Pan American World Airways: Blizzard advertisement: 1950 July 31
Pan American World Airways: Boeing 707 replica: 1959 Apr. 22
Pan American World Airways: Clipper "Am Worlderica": 1949 Mar. 7
Pan American World Airways: Douglas DC-8 jets: 1960 Jan. 20
Pan American World Airways: Fly Now-Pay Later: 1954 May 10
Pan American World Airways: Latin Am Worlderica Division: 1960 May 11
Pan American World Airways: New Horizons Club: 1955 Dec. 12
Pan American World Airways: New Jet services: 1958 July 14
Pan American World Airways: Norman Rockwell's art: 1956 Mar. 5
Pan American World Airways: Pacific-Alaska Division: 1957 May 13
Pan American World Airways: Student market: 1961 June 28
Pan American World Airways: Syverson cartoons: 1970 May 1
Parker Pen: 1949 Feb. 21; 1950 Apr. 24; 1950 Aug. 28.
Parker Pen: 51 pen--London: 1953 Dec. 7
Parker Pen: Christmas gift campaign: 1951 Oct. 8
Parker Pen: Liquid Lead pencil: 1955 Jan. 17
Parker Pen: Superchrome ink: 1947 June 16
Penick & Ford: 1948 Apr. 26
Penick & Ford: Molasses: 1953 Sept. 7
Pepsi Cola Co. of Canada--Montreal: 1947 Apr. 28
Pesquers Iquique (Frozen fish--Santiago): 1952 Aug. 4
Peter Robinson (Fashion shop--London): 1949 Sept. 19
Pharma-Craft:
Pharma-Craft: Colodene: 1956 Jan. 23; 1956 Nov. 5.
Pharma-Craft: Deodorant: 1955 Jan. 24; 1957 Apr. 1.
Pharma-Craft: Fresh (Deodorant): 1946 Sept. 2; 1947 May 19.
Phillips Petroleum (New client): 1962 Oct. 17
Pineapple Grower's Association: 1952 July 28
Pineapple Grower's Association: Fashion/Vogue: 1955 Apr. 11
Pineapple Grower's Association: Frosty pineapple pie: 1953 July 27
Pineapple Grower's Association: Ice Cream Festival: 1955 Oct. 17
Pittsburgh Plate Glass (Mirrors): 1961 Nov. 29
Portland Cement Association: 1957 Nov. 11; 1959 Mar. 25.
Prince Matchabelli, Inc. (Fragrance, Psyche): 1959 Sept. 9
Purolator: 1949 Aug. 15
Purolator: Car Clinic television series: 1961 Mar. 8
Purolator: Oil filter: 1955 Sept. 12
Purolator: Operation Virginia: 1954 Oct. 25
Quaker Oats:
Quaker Oats: Aunt Jemima: 1958 Feb. 17; 1960 Nov. 9; 1954 Aug. 30.
Quaker Oats: Humanized campaign: 1958 Oct. 6
Quaker Oats: Ken-L Ration dog food: 1959 Feb. 25
Quaker Oats: Life cereal: 1961 Mar. 22; 1958 Oct. 20.
Quaker Oats: Pancake campaign: 1957 Jan. 21
Quaker Oats: Quota weight loss: 1960 Nov. 16
R.T. French: 1947 Oct. 27
R.T. French: Mustard: 1956 Feb. 27; 1960 Aug. 17; 1961 Jan. 11.
R.T. French: Scalloped potatoes: 1960 Apr. 20
Radio Station CFRB--Toronto: 1948 Sept. 6
Radio station KNBC: 1951 July 9
Rayve Home Permanent: 1949 Jan. 17; 1950 June 12.
RCA: 1949 Mar. 28; 1952 June 30; 1960 Jan. 27.
RCA: 5 Ways Finer for '53: 1953 Jan. 5
RCA: Color television: 1960 Sept. 7
RCA: Disney/color television: 1961 Sept. 13
RCA: Golden Ear: 1953 Nov. 16
RCA: High school students: 1961 May 17
RCA: Institutional: 1948 Feb. 16; 1950 Jan. 2.
RCA: Instruments: 1946 Dec. 30
RCA: Octoputer: 1970 June 2
RCA: Records: 1947 Jan. 13; 1950 Nov. 6.
RCA: Television: 1953 Sept. 21; 1950 Jan. 30.
Reader's Digest: 1956 Dec. 17; 1956 Oct. 29; 1957 Oct. 28.
Reader's Digest: Network television campaign: 1960 Dec. 14
Reader's Digest: New client: 1956 Jan. 2
Reader's Digest: Public relations: 1961 May 10
Reckitt & Colman (Zubes cough suppressant--Capetown): 1949 Feb. 14
Religion in American Life: 1954 Oct. 4; 1956 Nov. 19; 1959 Sept. 16; 1960 Aug. 31.
Religion in American Life: Public service advertising: 1950 Oct. 30
Religion in American Life: Target young adults: 1958 Sept. 15
Religion in American Life: Thanksgiving: 1957 Nov. 25
Rice Industry: 1959 June 24
RKO Radio Pictures: 1956 July 2
Roddis Plywood Corp.: 1957 July 1
Rolex Watch Co.: 1955 Aug. 1
Rowntree's (Confectionary--London): 1953 Nov. 2
Royal Baking Powder:
Royal Baking Powder: Fairyland campaign--Capetown: 1952 Sept. 1
Royal Baking Powder: London: 1952 July 21
S.S. Jacobs Co.: 1955 May 9
Safeway Stores: 1952 Feb. 18
Safeway Stores: 25% sales increase: 1955 July 11
Safeway Stores: Economy campaign: 1955 Jan. 31
Safeway Stores: Famous flour: 1947 Sept. 22
Safeway Stores: Farm advertising: 1950 Aug. 7
Safeway Stores: Fleet biscuit mix: 1950 Feb. 6
Safeway Stores: Frozen chicken: 1955 June 6
Safeway Stores: Lucerne milk: 1949 June 13; 1955 Mar. 28.
Produce: 1954 May 31
Recruitment: 1955 May 2
San Francisco Chronicle: 1949 June 20
San Francisco Mutual Railway: 1950 June 26
Scarfe & Co., Ltd. (Jellied paint--Toronto): 1955 Apr. 4
Schlage Lock Co.: 1957 Dec. 30; 1961 Dec. 13.
Schlitz Brewing Co. (Joy of Living album): 1959 May 6
Scott Paper Co.: 1947 Oct. 20; 1951 Nov. 26; 1960 Jan. 6.
Scott Paper Co.: $15,000,000 buildings: 1961 June 21
Scott Paper Co.: Animated commercials: 1959 Apr. 15
Scott Paper Co.: Bringing Up Buddy television series: 1961 Jan. 25
Scott Paper Co.: Circus animal album: 1961 Aug. 30
Scott Paper Co.: Colored napkins: 1960 July 27
Scott Paper Co.: Cut-Rite: 1961 July 19
Scott Paper Co.: Magic Oval Box: 1962 Feb. 14
Scott Paper Co.: New Hankie Pack: 1961 Aug. 9
Scott Paper Co.: New with Colors: 1956 Apr. 2
Scott Paper Co.: Scot tissue: 1947 Feb. 24; 1955 Feb. 28.
Scott Paper Co.: Scot Towel: 1960 Apr. 13
Scott Paper Co.: Scotkins napkins: 1953 June 29
Scott Paper Co.: Scotkins: 1958 Mar. 3
Scott Paper Co.: Soft-Weve: 1949 Oct. 31; 1957 July 8.
Scott Paper Co.: Tri-Color: 1956 July 16
Scott Paper Co.: Two new television shows: 1961 Aug. 23
Scott Paper Co.: Waldorf Tissues: 1949 Dec. 19
Scripto, Inc. (Ink pens): 1956 Aug. 13
Sealy mattress (Posturepedic): 1959 Apr. 8
Seven-Up: 1946 Oct. 14; 1951 Dec. 10; 1959 Jan. 28.
Seven-Up: Fresh-Up Freddie: 1957 Dec. 2
Seven-Up: Kingston Trio: 1960 July 27
Seven-Up: Target teens: 1959 Dec. 30
Shell Chemical Corp.: 1947 Mar. 10; 1956 Sept. 17; 1958 June 23.
Shell Oil Co.: 1946 Nov. 4; 1950 Apr. 10; 1948 Oct. 11; 1949 Apr. 25.
Shell Oil Co.: Gasoline: 1952 Apr. 21
Shell Oil Co.: Local radio: 1947 Dec. 29
Shell Oil Co.: Oil: 1952 May 12
Shell Oil Co.: Outdoor advertising: 1947 June 2
Shell Oil Co.: Premium gasoline: 1951 May 14
Shell Oil Co.: Public Relations: 1946 Dec. 16
Shell Oil Co.: Radar Tests gasoline: 1956 Apr. 9
Shell Oil Co.: West Coast--public relations: 1949 July 18
Shell Oil Co.: X-100 motor oil: 1951 Apr. 30
Sherwin-Williams (Lin-X Home Brights--Montreal): 1948 Mar. 29
Siam di Tella (Motor scooter--Buenos Aires): 1954 Nov. 29
Singer (Wizard of Oz theme): 1970 Mar. 6
Southern California Citrus Foods: 1947 Mar. 17
Southwest Airways: 1950 Sept. 4
Squibb:
Squibb: Campaign against virus: 1954 May 3
Squibb: Squibb International: 1947 July 14
Stag Brewery--Johannesburg: 1953 Apr. 20
Standard Brands: 1950 Mar. 6
Standard Brands: Baking powder: 1955 July 25
Standard Brands: Chase & Sanborn: 1960 Feb. 10
Standard Brands: "Eat More Bread": 1956 Feb. 6
Standard Brands: Fleischmann's yeast: 1955 Jan. 10; 1952 Jan. 14; 1949 Mar. 14; 1951 July 2; 1960 Mar. 23.
Standard Brands: Instant tea: 1960 June 8
Standard Brands: New Tender Leaf: 1961 July 5
Standard Brands: Planters Peanuts: 1962 Jan. 24
Standard Brands: Recipes: 1956 Mar. 12
Standard Brands: Royal pudding: 1956 Dec. 24; 1960 Jan. 6; 1955 Feb. 14.
Standard Brands: Tea party: 1958 Apr. 7
Standard Brands: Tender Leaf Tea: 1961 Nov. 8; 1956 July 23; 1960 July 13.
Standard Brands: Tender Leaf tea--International: 1952 Nov. 24
Standard Brands: Young America Cooks: 1961 Oct. 18
Standard Brands Ltd.--Montreal:
Standard Brands Ltd.--Montreal: Chase & Sanborn: 1950 Aug. 14
Standard Brands Ltd.--Montreal: Magic baking powder: 1951 June 11
Staze, Inc. (Denture adhesive): 1951 Jan. 15
Steel Co. of Wales--London: 1958 Feb. 10
Stouffer Corp.:
Stouffer Corp.: Free offer: 1959 May 27
Stouffer Corp.: Television campaign: 1959 Nov. 11
Swift & Co.: 1947 Jan. 27; 1949 May 9; 1950 Apr. 3; 1950 Mar. 20; 1952 Mar. 3; 1954 Feb. 1.
Swift & Co.: Allsweet Margarine: 1956 Feb. 13
Swift & Co.: Bacon: 1950 Jan. 16
Swift & Co.: Bakery shortenings: 1949 Aug. 22
Swift & Co.: Centennial: 1955 Apr. 25
Swift & Co.: Dog food: 1952 Aug. 11; 1954 Jan. 18.
Swift & Co.: Franks, sausage: 1947 Oct. 13
Swift & Co.: Fresh meats: 1947 May 5
Swift & Co.: Grocery products: 1954 July 19
Swift & Co.: Ham, bacon: 1948 Jan. 19
Swift & Co.: Margarine: 1952 May 26
Swift & Co.: Pard dog food: 1948 Apr. 19; 1952 Oct. 20; 1955 Feb. 21.
Swift & Co.: Peanut butter: 1948 Sept. 20; 1950 Feb. 13.
Swift & Co.: Swift'ning: 1948 Mar. 22; 1949 July 25.
Swift & Co.: Table Ready meats: 1950 July 24
Swift & Co.: Vigoro plant food: 1953 Feb. 9; 1948 Mar. 15; 1951 Feb. 12.
Sylvania Electric Products:
Sylvania Electric Products: Fluorescent lamps: 1955 June 20
Sylvania Electric Products: Halolight: 1954 Dec. 20
Sylvania Electric Products: Softlight: 1956 July 9
Textron: 1946 Dec. 23
Textron: Corporate: 1970 May 15
Textron: Nashua Mills: 1948 Feb. 2
The Long Red Line (Blood drive): 1951 Dec. 17
Thomas A. Edison, Inc. (Voice Writer): 1956 Jan. 30
Times Weekly Edition--London: 1947 Aug. 4
Timken Roller Bearing Co.: 1954 Aug. 16
Trailer Coach Manufacturers' Association: 1949 Jan. 31; 1951 July 30.
Mobile Home Inspection Week 1952 Nov. 3
U.S. Brewer's Foundation: 1947 Apr. 7; 1947 Sept. 8; 1949 May 2; 1951 Feb. 5; 1952 Jan. 28; 1960 Aug. 3; 1960 July 20.
U.S. Brewer's Foundation: Home Life in America: 1953 May 18
U.S. Committee for Refugees (World Refugee Year): 1960 Apr. 6
U.S. Lines: 1951 July 16; 1962 Mar. 7.
SS United States: 1952 June 23
Superliner: 1952 June 9
Tourist market: 1959 Feb. 18
U.S. Marine Corps (Posters, direct mail): 1953 July 13
U.S. Playing Card Co.: 1946 Sept. 9; 1948 Oct. 25; 1958 July 28; 1960 Aug. 10.
United Artists (Beacon Pictures): 1947 July 7
United Crusade (Charity): 1955 Oct. 31
United Foundation (Charity): 1953 Oct. 19
United Medical Services (Increased benefits): 1955 Oct. 3
United Nations Day (Public service advertising): 1950 Oct. 16
United Tobacco Cos. Ltd. (Preference promotion--Capetown): 1953 Jan. 26
University of California Radiation Lab: 1957 Feb. 25
Ward Baking Co.: 1949 Aug. 1; 1952 June 2; 1956 June 4.
Ward Baking Co.: Emily Tipp campaign: 1958 Apr. 14
Ward Baking Co.: Gerber Primary bread: 1959 May 13
Ward Baking Co.: Tip Top bread: 1947 Feb. 3; 1953 Nov. 30.
Washington State Apple Commission: 1947 Dec. 1; 1949 Oct. 24; 1950 Oct. 23; 1952 Oct. 27.
Washington State Dairy Products Commission (Teenage study): 1951 Oct. 22
Weco Products Co.: 1948 Jan. 5; 1949 Oct. 3; 1951 Mar. 26.
Wells Organizations, Inc. (Church fund raising): 1954 Sept. 6
Western Union: 1947 Feb. 10; 1949 Oct. 17.
Westminster Tobacco Co.--Capetown: 1951 July 23
Whitbread & Co. (Beer--Antwerp): 1957 Sept. 2
Whizzer Motor Co.: 1948 Dec. 13; 1948 May 31; 1947 May 12.
Window Shade Institute: 1949 Apr. 18
Woods Manufacturing Co.--Montreal: 1949 June 27
Wool Bureau: 1957 Aug. 12; 1958 Aug. 4; 1960 Feb. 10.
Wool Bureau Inc. & Wool Inc.: 1954 July 12; 1956 Oct. 15.
Yankee Baseball Team: 1947 Oct. 6
Yellow Cab Co.: 1950 Dec. 4
News Bulletin Contents by Author
Materials located in Boxes MN1-MN5.
Acland, Peregrine. It Takes Too Much Time to Sell Bulk Goods 1925 Sept.
Acland, Peregrine. Make a Sale Every Time You Get an Interview 1926 June
Anderson, Harriet. End of the Era of Humbug 1923 July
Anderson, Hayward. Be Yourself! But Can You? 1929 Dec.
Anderson, Margaret. Why Is Your Copy So Long? 1922 Mar.
Angell, Norman. New Factor in Social Development 1928 Mar.
Ardery, Lois. She Wants It But She Doesn't Know It Yet 1924 Dec.
Ashby, Bruce. Are the Makers of Automotive Accessories on the Horns of a Sales Dilemma? 1927 Feb.
Ashby, Bruce. Farmer's Dollar and How It Is Spent 1927 Jan.
Ashby, Bruce. What About the Farm Market? 1926 July
Aymar, Gordon C.. Advertising Illustration in England 1929 Apr.
Aymar, Gordon C.. Munsell Color System 1922 Dec.
Aymar, Gordon C.. What Advertising Has Done for Type Design 1923 June
Aymar, Gordon C.. What Will Follow the Rule of Thumb Era? 1922 Aug.
Barnes, Julius H.. Economic Marketing 1925 Mar.
Berridge, William. Index of the Incomes of Factory Workers 1924 Mar.
Boren, Wallace R.. Mental Lunch Counters for Consumers 1930 May
Browne, Raymond. Selective Distribution 1929 Mar.
Casseres, Aminta. Headlines! Did You Ever Write a Good One? 1922 Dec.
Casseres, Aminta. How Important is the Style of the Copy? 1923 July
Casseres, Aminta. Radio Today is Not Just a Good-Will Medium 1929 Oct.
Cherington, Paul T.. Can Advertising Effects Be Measured? 1927 Apr.
Cherington, Paul T.. Chain Stores in the Grocery Business 1927 Sept.
Cherington, Paul T.. College Education for Business 1925 Aug.
Cherington, Paul T.. Distribution Census and Trends in Retailing 1929 Oct.
Cherington, Paul T.. Economic Phases of Advertising 1927 June
Cherington, Paul T.. Editorial Character of Business Papers 1926 Jan.
Cherington, Paul T.. Fallacy of Salesman Research 1930 Apr.
Cherington, Paul T.. Fruit of the Loom Decision 1922 Nov.
Cherington, Paul T.. Lo: The Cliff Dweller 1927 Sept.
Cherington, Paul T.. Manufacturer's Relations to Jobber's and Retailer's Salesmen 1923 Apr.
Cherington, Paul T.. New Practices in the Construction of Sales Quotas 1927 Jan.
Cherington, Paul T.. Outline of the New Book Retail Shopping Areas 1928 Mar.
Cherington, Paul T.. Rose By Any Other Name 1922 Sept.
Cherington, Paul T.. Scientific Methods in Agency Work 1923 July
Cherington, Paul T.. Securities Panic 1929 Dec.
Cherington, Paul T.. Some Fundamental Principles of Organization 1927 Mar.
Cherington, Paul T.. Some Lessons from Early New England Foreign Trading 1923 June
Cherington, Paul T.. Some Marketing Problems of the Shoe Industry 1925 Feb.
Cherington, Paul T.. Some Recent Changes in the Rural and Small Town Market 1925 July
Cherington, Paul T.. Some Recent Developments in Market Analysis 1927 May
Cherington, Paul T.. Standard Color Scheme for Market Analysis Charts 1925 Oct.
Cherington, Paul T.. Where Are You Going--My Pretty Market? 1926 Nov.
Cherington, Paul T.. Where the Urban and Rural Population Live 1924 Jan.